Found Antigravity [Google.Antigravity]
Version: 1.18.3
Publisher: Google
Publisher Url: https://www.google.com/
Publisher Support Url: https://antigravity.google/support
Author: Google LLC
Description: Google Antigravity is an agentic development platform, evolving the IDE into the agent-first era. Antigravity enables developers to operate at a higher, task-oriented level managing agents across workspaces, while retaining a familiar AI IDE experience at its core. Antigravity extracts agents into their own surface and provides them the tools needed to autonomously operate across the editor, terminal, and browser emphasizing verification and higher-level communication via tasks and artifacts. This capability enables agents to plan and execute more complex, end-to-end software tasks, elevating all aspects of development, from building features, UI iteration, and fixing bugs to research and generating reports.
Homepage: https://antigravity.google/
License: Proprietary
License Url: https://antigravity.google/terms
Privacy Url: https://policies.google.com/privacy
Copyright Url: https://antigravity.google/terms
Release Notes:
  Settings, Artifacts, and Stability
  New settings screens for models and terminal integration, artifact download support, and various stability and UI fixes across platforms.
  Improvements (5)
  - Added Models screen to settings, providing more visibility into quota usage.
  - Added a setting to enable or disable terminal integration.
  - Support for downloading artifacts from the chat UI.
  - Up/down arrow key navigation for input box history.
  - Improved UI responsiveness for chat interactions, including creating conversations, sending messages, and reverting changes.
  Fixes (3)
  - Resolved an issue where external plugins could fail to load on macOS due to signing problems.
  - Fixed certain artifact files not being recognized as artifacts and missing the 'Proceed' button in the chat UI on Windows.
  - Fixed an issue where reverting could occasionally delete files edited by the agent.
  Patches (0)
Release Notes Url: https://antigravity.google/changelog
Purchase Url: https://antigravity.google/pricing
Documentation:
  Docs: https://antigravity.google/docs
Tags:
  code
  coding
  develop
  development
  editing
  editor
  programming
Installer:
  Installer Type: inno
  Installer Url: https://edgedl.me.gvt1.com/edgedl/release2/j0qc3/antigravity/stable/1.18.3-4739469533380608/windows-x64/Antigravity.exe
  Installer SHA256: 6e1ff051a061b595daede6f0177b390a9239dc094c39ee6992f69f9d19377ea6
  Release Date: 2026-02-19
  Offline Distribution Supported: true
